socialsolutions.com 2005-04-09

# Social Solutions, Inc

Privacy Policy

**Updated: November 1, 2003**

Your use of our online resources may result in Social Solutions, Inc. (Social Solutions) collecting information about you. Your privacy and its protection are of utmost importance to our entire team. Therefore, this policy has been established to communicate with you our commitment to your privacy as well as how your information will by used by our team.

Data Collection

When you use Social Solution’s online resources, information may be collected in 3 different ways:

Web Site Traffic—Web site traffic is collected by our web server. It tells us where individuals go on our site, which pages are most popular, how much time users spend in certain sections, etc. It helps us to analyze the effectiveness of our web-site and guides us in making it a better resource for you. 

Cookies—Cookies allow web sites to maintain personal information and/or online history on an individual's computer. This information, when read by a web server, allows the site to be customized to every user. At this time Social Solution’s web site uses cookies to facilitate login. These cookies do not collect information about the user or computer that is accessing our site. The cookie information is not collected by the web server. 

Request For Information—An individual can request information from our team by navigating to the appropriate page and entering the personal information requested. In doing so, the user recognizes they are doing so voluntarily. The information collection falls into two categories: That which is required to be certain the information can properly get to the requester, and that which is voluntary and meant to assist the Social Solution’s team with the task of delivering an appropriate response to the requester. 

We do not knowingly collect information from children. All requests for information are assumed to be from adults. If we determine that any information has been collected from children, we will do our best to purge it immediately.

Data Analysis

As indicated above, Social Solutions collects usage statistics from our web server and third party applications providers as one of several analysis methods to make our site and communications more useful to our visitors.

We may analyze the information collected from the Contact Us page as one of several methods to better understand the markets that we serve.

Data Sharing

While we will make every effort to protect and preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose some or all information when required to do so by law or by order of a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served to us and/or our web site. In such case, Social Solutions will only share the information when we have a good-faith belief that doing so is necessary to legally comply.

In the event that Social Solutions merges with, is acquired by, or sells some of its assets to any other interest, the information that has been collected from this site may be transferred as part of the transaction.

In all other cases, Social Solutions will not share or distribute your personal information with any third party without that party's explicit approval.

Communications From the Social Solutions Team

The information collected from this site will be used to communicate with you. Submission of your information on the Contact Us page indicates your willingness to receive information from Social Solutions into the future. See the Participation section below for instructions on how to remove yourself from our communications lists.

Participation

You have the following rights concerning the personal information that we may collect through this site:

* Request if we have collected or are collecting information about you 

* Request a copy of the information that we have collected 

* Request that we purge all information collected about you and stop collecting your information 

* At the time of the request, we reserve the right to ask that you provide proof of your identity. We also reserve the right to deny your request based on your inability to provide identity proof.

To make any of the above requests, please contact Adrian@SocialSolutionsOnline.com

Partner Links

In different areas of our site you will see links to other sites that are owned and operated by our business partners and third party affiliates. This policy does not cover the information contained within or gathered by those sites, and we are not responsible for their privacy policies.

Security

We have implemented reasonable technology and security policies to ensure the quality and integrity as well as protect the security of any personal information we may have collected from you. Our employees are obliged to respect your privacy and the confidentiality of your information.

Notification of Changes

As we create new services through this site, we may need to amend this privacy policy. To help you determine when and how our policy has changed, the most current revision date of this document will be noted on our home page, and a summary of the most recent changes will be annotated at the top of this document.

Questions

For all other inquiries about this privacy policy please contact:

Adrian Bordone, Vice President

3500 Boston Street, Suite 70

Baltimore, MD 21224

Phone: 410.732.3560 or 866.732.3560

Fax: 410.732.3561

Email: Adrian@SocialSolutionsOnline.com
